<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="91433" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="InfoLoom" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Adds 11 new UI windows that lets the user see their statistics about their city" />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>## Info Loom
- **Most of the credit goes to Infixo for making the original version of this mod, I just updated and made sure it worked properly and updated the UI.**
- **Adds 11 new UI windows and a new settings option to the game, which are Demographics,Workforce structure and Workplace distribution, Residential data, Demand factors, Commercial Data, Industrial and Office Data, Commercial Products, Industrial and office Data.**

###Currently:
- Demographics
- Workforce structure
- Workplace distribution 
- Residential data 
- Commercial data
- Industrial and Office data
- Demand factors
- Production types ui (Commercial and Industrial)
- Trade costs		
- Districts		

### Demographics
- Key information about current city demographics in one place.
- Age distribution histogram that also shows cims' activity structure.
NEW - show grouped age view.
NEW - summary statistics for each age group.

### Workforce structure
- Shows workforce structure by education level.
- Total: all potential workers, i.e. teens and adults, that are moved in and not moving away, excluding students.
- Unemployment by education level and structure also shown as percentage.
- Under: cims working on positions below their education level.
- Outside: cims working outside of the city.
- Homeless: unemployed cims with no home.

### Workplace distribution
- Shows available workplaces split into: city services, commercial sales, commercial leisure, industry extractors, industry manufacturing, and office.
- Commute are cims employed from outside of the city, they commute to work.
- Shows number of companies in each category.

### Residential data
- Shows residential data used to calculate Residential Demand Factors.
- Residential properties by density: total count, occupied, free.
- Total households and homeless households.
- Average happiness, weighted tax rate, open study positions.
- Household demand which is hidden in the game, it controls if new households spawn.
- For new households, a chance that a Student Household will spawn.

### Demand factors
- Shows individual demand factor VALUES for each demand type. Helpful to learn actual importance of each factor.
- Enables showing all demand factors, not only 5. (Useful for industrial demand which is the only one that utilizes up to 7 factors. This may have changed in recent updates).
- Additional section shows directly building demand for each zone type and STORAGE demand. Please note that the "main" demand factor is actually a building demand, however UI shows it as moving. In fact it doesn't move, it is just a visualization.
- Also, industrial demand is a higher value from the two: industrial building demand and storage demand.

### Commercial data
- Shows commercial data used to calculate Commercial Demand Factors.
- Empty buildings and companies that have no property, and average tax rate.
- Service capacity utilization and sales capacity to consumption ratio - these are crucial in calculating LocalDemand, TouristDemand and PetrolLocalDemand.
- Actual numbers of available workforce, and employee capacity ratio.
- Lists resources that currently are not demanded, thus the engine ignores them when calculating Commercial Demand Factors.

### Industrial and Office data
- Shows industrial and office data used to calculate Industrial and Office Demand Factors.
- Empty buildings and companies that have no property, and average tax rate.
- Local Demand (which is production capacity in fact) and Input Utilization (which tells if resources are available as input).
- Actual numbers of available workforce, and employee capacity ratio.
- Lists resources that currently are not demanded, thus the engine ignores them when calculating Industrial and Office Factors.
- Storage section that shows Demanded Types info which controls if new warehouses are spawned.

### Commercial Products
- Demand (1): resource demand - key number that decides what companies will spawn; negative value will block spawning; the higher the number, the higher probability of a company being spawned.
- Demand (2): zone demand - key number that decides what buildings will spawn; 0 means there is no demand.
- Free: number of free properties (buildings) for companies selling the specific resource.
- Num: number of companies.
- service:  factor and percentage vs. maximum service.
- Household needs: percentage vs. Resource Need, and average capacity per company.
- Workers: percentage vs. maximum workers, and total workers.
- Tax: tax factor.

### Industrial and Office Data
- Demand (1): resource demand - key number that decides what companies will spawn; negative value will block spawning; the higher the number, the higher probability of a company being spawned.
- Demand (2): Industrial Company demand - key number that decides what buildings/company will spawn; 0 means there is no demand.
- Free: number of free properties (buildings) for companies selling the specific resource.
- Num: number of companies.
- storage buildings:  number of storage buildings
- Production and demand : How much is being produced and how much resource is needed (this may differ or work completly different for office demand)
- Workers: percentage vs. maximum workers, and total workers.
- Tax: tax factor.

### Districts 
- shows District name
- number of households 
- number of residents
- number of pets
- number of employees
- employment data 
- education data
- district average wealth		

### Option in settings 
- control the tax strength for commercial products when taxing individual products.

### Credit
- Dava787: screenshot of the Workplace distribution UI
- Nullpinter: Improved UI		
	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/InfoLoom.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/Demographics.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/Workforce.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/WorkplaceDistribution.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/Demand.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/ResidentialData.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/CommercialData.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/IndustrialOfficeData.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshots/Products.png" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/info-loom.1707423/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.8.0" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.2.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog>## Version 1.8.0
- Fixed Demographics UI dropdown not working properly
- Fixed InfoLoom menu submenu panels closing when the infoLoom menu was closed 
- Added Resource Icons instead of using resource name in the commercial and industrial company data UI	
- Added Profitability to the commercial and industrial company data UI and some related extra information to the profitability tooltips 
- Redesigned Workplace and Workforce UI panels to just show more tables instead of unnecessary information
</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon, buymeacoffee, kofi, crowdin, gitlab-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/bruceyboy24804/InfoLoom" />
	<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/jPafqgUU" />
</Publish>
	